During the Monday service at the SCOAN
Prophet TB Joshua is ministering prayer and deliverance
in the name of Jesus Christ.
The name above all names is power and fire
which causes satan and his agents to tremble and flee.
As the man of God prays for this man, demons within him manifest violently.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Why are you disturbing me?
He was donated to me by his great grandfather.
When he was seven 7 days old, I wanted to take him; they dedicated him to me.
(Who are you?)
Idol from the father's house.
(What have you done to him?)
I have used him in so many ways.
(Explain!)
He's meant to serve me!
He has no career, has no future.
He has a heart of helping, but I can't allow him.
I have destroyed him in so many ways
I have destroyed him in giving him so many sicknesses - cancer!
Every evil thing you can think of - I have made him do.
He womanises.
I have destroyed his family; his family is nothing to write home about - all of them.
I took the mother. I took his father. I gave his daughter cancer.
I gave him cancer
Even his first son is not even talking for five years now.
- Who caused it?!
- I did!
Who are you?
Idol from his father's house.
How did you enter this body?
He was dedicated to me
when he was seven days old.
Satan and his agents are powerless in the face of God's might and the man is delivered in seconds.
Thank you, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
People of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good morning church.
My name is Mr. Prince Obaerechi
The lady beside me is my wife.
It all started like this:
when I was 10 -12 years old, I noticed something unusual happening,
but those were things that I could not be able to control on my own.
Sometimes I went against my wish to do them,
but after doing those things I would feel so guilty for doing them and tomorrow I would still do them again.
Things like...
At the age 10-12 years I had a group of friends, living in the same neighbourhood.
... things like stealing little things from the people in the community.
I started from stealing money from my mothers handbag and using it...
At the end of the day, when asked, I would deny stealing it.
It went on like that for so many years.
When I was growing up, I noticed that something was wrong,
but I couldn't "fish out" what really was happening.
In 2006 I lost my mother.
After the burial, my mum's sister called a family meeting,
saying that there was something that they wanted to tell me.
I asked what it was.
They told me that when I was born...
From the first day I was delivered here on earth, I cried continually for 7 days.
My mother had no option but to take me to her father, who happened to be a very strong native doctor.
He never wore anything on his feet until when he died.
Every thing in his compound was a shrine - he was as strong as that.
Nevertheless, he wasn't able to find solution, so he went to another bigger witch doctor.
They consulted the witch doctor and he said that he was the one who came back as an incarnation,
that he wasn't supposed to be alive, that he was supposed to die before he came back.
But there's was nothing the man could have done.
They asked what they could do - he said that either they leave me to die,
or they go and buy things mentioned to them.
They were told to go to 3 junctions and perform some sacrifices, by 12 am.
After the sacrifice...
The man would die for me to live.
It was a very big problem in the house.
They went back home.
The father of my mother had so many wives but he loved my mum, as his first daughter.
He never wanted to disappoint my mum.
One day he called a meeting and said that he is going to do the sacrifice.
They asked him what would happen after the sacrifice.
He told them that they should keep me behind; when I grow up I would continue where he stopped.
So, they went and purchased the items mentioned to them by the "bigger" witch-doctor they went to.
By 12 am the sacrifice was conducted
After few days the man died.
That is how I stopped crying.
The story did not make sense to me,
I asked why was the story coming then?
Why didn't it come before, when my mother was alive?
The woman told me that she was the only woman who was living with my mum at that time.
She knew everything that happened.
But later the woman repented; she was the deaconess in the Assembly of God church.
My mum also repented.
However they Ignored the idol.
I never knew, all this years, that the idol was living in me and walking in me.
As the time went by, I was growing up and the story didn't mean anything to me.
I started hanging out with my old friends.
Some of those friends grown up to be mature, having their own gangs.
Sometimes they could call me and we would go to people houses and burgle them,
and take them away; sometimes we took money from them.
One strange thing always happened.
If I kept looking at a glass cup on the desk and I would be imagining that glass cup will fall down and break;
I would be imagining for 4 or 5 minutes, then and you would see that glass cup fall down and break.
If anybody offended me, they must have had a big problem, leading to accident, or...
You must get yourself in a very big problem.
I was very proud of it.
During those days, I made a lot of money.
I was using big cars, I made money; the money was coming.
You made us to understand that it was immediately after the death of the father of your mother,
when this spirit fully possessed you.
- Is that correct?
- Yes.
- You were said to be his incarnation?
- And he was a notorious witch doctor during his time?
- Yes.
It goes this way:
If you have a mission to carry out...
We thought that we were very smart and intelligent.
We would go to a witch doctor for a consultation
During the consultation we were called to look in the mirror,
and the witch doctor would tell you if you would make it or not.
He would tell you if you are going to succeed or not.
If there was a problem, you would have to fortify yourself before the journey.
When we entered the house, I didn't need to ask where the money was; I knew it.
I would go straight where the money was and I would pick it.
That is how it was working for me.
In 2010, I noticed a problem - a growth that became bigger at daily basis.
Another time I noticed other growth on my hip; this one was growing bigger than the first one.
So I hid it to myself; I didn't want to tell anybody.
I started going to hospitals.
There is no hospital in Nigeria that I did not go to.
I went to witch-doctors.
I went to prayer houses.
I went to many churches, which I don't want to call names - many churches.
I didn't want to die, because all these years I thought I was careful not to lose my life.
But this sickness came.
I would have gone to any place, no matter the cost.
There was a place, where I told a man, "If my health was going to cost a human head - tell me."
I was ready.
When the health issue stepped in, I started selling things because all my money was gone.
As there was no solution, I started selling my properties, cars, but at end of the day nothing happened.
The person that bought my last car asked me, "Why can't you go to the Synagogue?"
I said, "Stop telling me that."
We used to read papers, where they castigated the man of God, and wrote rubbish about him.
We found it very comfortable to neglect the existence of God.
Because there was someone castigating the man of God, we could say, "There was no God".
Our conclusion was that all of them were the same.
I asked him, if he wanted to escape paying my money.
I wanted to treat myself, I had spent all my money; I sold my car...
He told me of somebody who had diabetes, who had come and had received the Morning Water;
he was healed before he got home.
I told him to stop all those stories .
Then a friend of mine, who resides in Bayelsa State, was burying his mother;
I went to his mothers burial.
I then opened up to him, telling him what I was going through.
He is a member of this church.
He asked me If I had gone to The SCOAN.
I asked him to leave that conversation.
He tried preaching to me.
While the hearse was still going, he told me that I needed to go to The SCOAN.
I said I didn't want to go there, but he insisted.
At that time he provoked me and said, "Young man, if you choose to want to know God; - know God.
If you choose not to want to know God - leave it. This life is a battlefield and not a playground."
After he had said this I was contemplating, "This word is a battlefield and not a playground.
If you choose to want to know God - know God
if you don't want - leave it"
At that time, these words kept ringing inside my mind.
When I tried to forget about it, it didn't go away easily.
It became as a little stream in my heart that refused to get dry.
At that time, there was a hotel I used to stay in.
At that time, I didn't go out "openly"; I always went to the rural areas and lodged there,
so that those who knew me would not see me.
So, I was staying in the hotel.
When all my hope was lost, I called one of my brothers, a friend.
I told him, "Young man I've seen my death. I know that I am going to die but before I die,
look at how my burial would happen."
After that conversation with him, I began to scatter things in the room.
Somebody that was inside with me said that I should cool down I would not die.
In the meantime, the television went off in my hotel room.
Somebody was trying to fix it I found Emmanuel TV.
When Emmanuel TV was on...
I began to watch, I saw testimonies, healing and many things.
I wondered if this was the same man that they said things about.
Yet, I had not been convinced.
At the end of the day, I said to myself, "I went to herbal homes, prayer-houses, churches;
let me also go there."
I came only to try, like I tried in other places before.
When I came to the gate, a voice spoke to me to go back.
I went back to my hotel.
A friend advised me to go to India.
I went to India; this was my first time I was in India...
This is a medical visa.
I went and came back, I want to max hospital
and I spent three months nothing happened.
I came back, I went back to another hospital in India,
I spent three months there and I came back.
I went back there again to "Action Cancer" hospital in New Delhi, in India.
When I came back, they asked me to come back to SCOAN, since I already was in India.
The last time I was in India, the doctor asked me, "Who did I come with?"
I said, I hadn't come with anybody.
He left.
There was a young man I met in the flat while I was going; he had somebody there...
I told him, "Look, where I'm going".
I gave him my number.
After few days, the person who received my number called me and they located me.
The man said that since there was nobody with me, he wanted to assist me.
He took me to the "Action cancer" hospital, where I was before.
During my first medical check-up, the doctor shook his head, and he was a senior doctor.
He shook his head and asked me to go, and the man who was with me stayed with the doctor.
When the man came out, he was sweating.
I asked him what happened.
He said that I needed some relative to sign medical documents,
and he couldn't do it because he didn't know me, and anything could happen.
He began to tell me the stories of people who came from Nigeria with cancer and died.
My mind was troubled.
I asked him to go with me back to the doctor.
Doctor told me that he was giving me only 25% of chances.
Before, I heard that doctors would give 50/50 of chances, but in my case they gave only 25%.
I asked why they gave me so low chances.
I was scared.
I came back to Nigeria and I received Morning Water and I went home.
When I arrived home I was not satisfied.
I submitted request for another passport to make a trip.
It takes four days to obtain visa.
In the meantime my leg and my manhood have swollen.
I couldn't have worn shorts or trousers - I had to wear loose clothing.
If you had pressed any part of my body, it would not return to its place.
The pain was unbearable - you wouldn't wish it to anybody.
When I got the Morning Water, I started to minister it and the pain went away;
a pain that previously made me to run naked at midnight...
So, the Morning Water...
Mr & Mrs Prince Obaerechi
Deliverance Testimony
That is not enough for Jesus Christ; put you hands together beautifully for the miracle working God.
You made us to understand that as consequence of your involvement in acts of immorality,
experiencing the influence of the spirit possessing you from the childhood,
you were afflicted with a pelvic cancer.
People were hearing to your story, how sever it was; they would like to see it pictorially.
Can you show us on pictures what are you talking about, before you continue?
People will see how severe the case was, for them to know that satan has nothing to offer,
apart from affliction.
This is how it was, when I came first time.
By the time I entered the gate, one spirit told me to go back and I went back and travelled to India.
There, they gave me 25% of surviving and I came back to Nigeria.
When I came back, this is the way it was - as you can see...
These things are my flesh, and these is my lap; the cancer had shrunk...
As you see, my manhood was affected; it was very large.
It gave an intensive and offensive smell.
When I got the Morning Water, I started to minister it.
Before the visa came, I noticed that this unbearable pain was gone.
I said, "The pain is gone - OK..."
Mr & Mrs Prince Obaerechi
Deliverance Testimony
I said, "OK, since this pain is gone, we will see what happens next".
Day after day I kept seeing changes; the swelling leg started to shrink, so I was able to wear trousers.
I picked up the visa, but I didn't use the passport.
I said that something was happening.
When I calmed down, I was very happy.
When the leg shrunk down, I began to watch the wound and minister the Morning Water to it.
In the hospital they told me that I shouldn't pour water on the wound.
When I saw that the wound was shrinking I kept ministering the Morning Water to it.
The wound kept drying... I was very surprised, till it came like this...
OK, just a moment.
Before you finally saw the changes, you travelled to India twice, in search of solution?
- Yes, sir.
- All to no avail?
And you said you had been preparing for the third visit to India?
Yes.
But after receiving the Morning Water, when you started to see changes, you resigned to go to India?
Perfectly correct, sir.
And you got your healing in the ministry you were criticizing?
OK, can you go to the board and show the present condition of your pelvic?
After ministering the Morning Water, the situation finally looks like this - I'm OK, no pain.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
You can see on the screen of you TV his present condition, as he stands in our midst.
There is a clear proof that after the ministration of the Morning Water,
the pelvic cancer is completely gone.
And for the benefit of the viewers all over the world; could you just tap the place right now,
and tell us how you are feeling?
How are you feeling?
Nothing, I don't feel anything; it's already gone, as I'm talking to you...
Before, I couldn't even dare to...
You couldn't do like this before?
I couldn't even try it, or get close to that place.
Why you couldn't do it then?
Because of the pain.
The thing was huge - it was a cancer of lymphoma, it can come on any part of the body.
- But now you are completely free?
- Yes, sir.
The cancer is gone, and the pain is gone?
- You are healed and healthy?
- Yes, sir.
Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ once again!
I started having those dreams, as if I was in the past.
I would see myself in the village, with my gang; we were very small.
The friend for mine said, "Let's go to a witch-doctor".
I said OK.
He said he didn't have money.
I gave him money and he went.
When he came back he told me, "Yes, this is a place to be."
I said, "OK. I want to go to that place, since it is a place to be there."
I went to that place.
They cut my finger, took my hair, marked my chest and feet and put my blood on a calabash.
They directed me to the shrine, telling to ask for anything I wanted.
After this... the only thing they eat in the shrine is blood.
I made some promises and I came back.
The whole thing became worse.
When I came back I hated myself, "Why did I go there?"
Something inside of me said, "Forget about it."
That's how I got to know two human natures existing in you;
one will be telling you positive things, the other the negative ones.
The one you choose to follow, that one will work for you.
At the end of the day...
Three weeks ago I was in the dream and it was said that the man of God would be coming somewhere.
I said I would go there.
I went to the place.
When I came to the place I saw people in white garments, but I didn't see the man of God there.
I looked on the front and I saw man of God touching people,
and I run to man of God to touch me - I slumped.
When I slumped, it looked like I was confessing something, but I didn't know what I was saying.
Later I got up.
Can you tell us who the man of God you are talking about was?
Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mr & Mrs Prince Obaerechi
Deliverance Testimony
When I woke I began to have this "disturbance"; the voice would say, "Go to Synagogue",
when I'm eating, "Go to Synagogue", when I take a bath, "Go to Synagogue".
After two days of having that dream, when it became to much, around 2:30 pm,
I picked up my luggages and I entered a cab to go to Lagos.
Normally, at that time you wouldn't see any vehicle coming to Lagos.
Inside the cab I was uncomfortable, until I fell asleep.
When I woke up I saw myself in Lagos.
On Sunday I was at the service; man of God started a mass prayer.
During that mass prayer I noticed that my chest, stomach, system - everything just changed.
My mouth were full; because I don't like watching people vomit - it irritates me.
I didn't want to vomit.
When I opened my mouth, I vomited so many things.
I was very happy; my body calmed down.
On Monday, I was here.
When the man of God was laying hands on people...
When there were only two people before mu turn, I noticed that I was shaking, all my body was vibrating.
I couldn't even look at his face.
Just now I see when he touched me, and I don't know what happened.
I woke up and saw myself being finally delivered.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
Eventually, you were delivered that Monday, as you can see on the left-hand side of the TV screen.
You made us to understand that you were unconscious, and you didn't know what happened,
until now, as you watch the video clip.
Now, tell us...
We believe...
You experience it, and your body knows it.
Tell us what are the changes you have seen in your life.
Compare your life before the deliverance and after the deliverance.
Before the deliverance, normally I had those dreams with women molesting me.
When I woke up, I would find myself wet.
I always had that spirit of lust.
I never had a rest, a peace of mind.
But since that Monday, I slept peacefully; somebody had to wake me up.
Somebody was complaining that there was a mosquito, but I didn't even feel it.
I was sleeping, I was at peace.
In the dream I was fighting people and killing them; so many of them.
When I woke up, I was even afraid.
I told the dream to my friend and he said it was a good dream.
OK, in other words, God gave you victory over the demons that were attacking you in the dream?
Perfectly correct, sir.
OK, now, tell us, what changes you have seen on your body.
Concerning the spirit of lust - is it over?
Concerning the spirit of anger - is it over?
What about your relationship with your family members?
What can you say about that after your deliverance?
Before now...
My wife can testify that while I'm angry I could put down this building within five minutes.
Yes.
I didn't go angry more than three times in a year, because my anger spoils things.
And I would never regret spoiling things.
But I noticed that I take things more lightly, since the deliverance.
I would just overlook those things.
On Tuesday, somebody called me from Abuja with an information of federal contract for me.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!
I have two advices.
One is for the parents: "Sometimes the things you do to help your children, can destroy them.
When you have parental issues, try to look for God first, before any other thing."
Two; the youth out there who is watching me right now,
"When you grow up, you will start noticing changes - things that are not normal in your life.
I wouldn't advise you to go to churches; I went to churches, to herbal homes, witch-doctors;
they couldn't deliver me.
I came to The SCOAN, the place I didn't want to hear about, here I got my deliverance.
Make haste! Don't waste time! Find yourself in the arena of liberty.
That God that saw me through, will definitely see you through!"
To God be the glory.
Yes, we believe that our membership in local churches is merely symbolic.
What counts is Christ in you; the hope of glory.
We believe that summary of the advice is that everyone should make haste,
and look for Jesus Christ in any living church - is that true?
- Yes, sir.
- To God be the glory.
Emmanuel!
(God with us.)
Good morning church.
My name is Elizabeth Obaerechi.
This is my lovely husband Mr Obaerechi.
Even before I married him, I knew he was a bad guy...
He told me that nobody could deliver him - that is what he always was saying.
No human could talk to him.
I just want to thank this great God of Prophet T.B. Joshua; that God used him to deliver my husband.
To God be the glory.
Amen! Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
We thank you so much for your patience all this while; you didn't give up on God,
you were with him to see this very day of his glorious testimony.
What is your advice to women like you, out there?
Yes, I thank God, that Prophet T.B. Joshua is still alive; you must be delivered,
so my happiness will be complete.
I thank God...
I want to give an advice to the fellow women, like me: they should be patient and trust God.
Nothing is impossible for God to do.
Amen! Let's clap for Jesus Christ for that.
To God be the glory.
Finally, we thank God Almighty for what He has done in the life of your husband and your own,
for giving you enough patience to bear the situation with him, until present moment,
when he is glorifying God with his testimony.
Remember, the deliverance, the healing came through the Word of God,
and we advise you to go and make the Word of God the standard for your lives.
As you do so, always have at the back of you minds that better is not good enough,
the best is always yet to come.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle working God!